Guide to The Impact of coeducation on Yale's alumnae, 1973-1983 by Julie M. Heller, Class of 1988, Yale College
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
The Impact of Coeducation on Yale's Alumnae, 1973-1983, by Julie M. Heller, Class of 1988, Yale College
1967-1988
RU 96
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.5
(3 boxes)
The materials consist of drafts, background articles, excerpts from reports, newspaper articles, and questionnaires assembled by Julie M. Heller (Yale 1988) for her senior essay titled, The Impact of Coeducation on Yale's Alumnae, 1973-1983.
Heller, Julie M.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 49 (YRG 49), Papers and projects on Yale.
Conditions Governing Access
While this collection as a whole is available for research, parts of it may be restricted due to law, university policy or fragility. Any restricted material will be noted as such.
Arrangement
Arranged by material type.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of drafts, background articles, excerpts from reports, newspaper articles, and questionnaires assembled by Julie M. Heller (Yale 1988) for her senior essay titled, The Impact of Coeducation on Yale's Alumnae, 1973-1983.
Coeducation; Women college students; Women -- Education; Essays; Heller, Julie M.; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University -- Students
- "The Impact of Co-education on Yale's Alumnae, 1973-1983", Accession 1989-A-001
  - Heller, Julie (Senior Thesis): "The Impact of Co-education on Yale's Alumnae, 1973-1983", 1988 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Prelimary Drafts, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bibliographical Materials, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Magazine and Journal Articles, 1970-1987 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yale Undergraduate Women's Caucus: Freshwoman's booklet (Excerpts), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Vassar-Yale Report from the Joint Study Committee" (Excerpts), 1967 September (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - "Report to the President from the University Committee on the Education of Women" (Excerpts), 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - "Report to the President from the University Committee on the Education of Women" (Excerpts), 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cowan, Dorrit Ann (Dissertation): "Single-sex to Co-education at Princeton and Yale" (Excerpts), 1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Survey Questionnaires, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Material is restricted until July 1, 2064 for privacy reasons.